https://www.osmh.on.ca/privacy/

About Us About UsOur Mission, Vision, ValuesOur HistoryBoard of DirectorsInformation RequestsCommunity EngagementVendor TablesQuality Improvement PlanAccountabilityPatients & Visitors Patients & VisitorsAccessibilityComing In For An AppointmentFor Your SafetyHospital ServicesPatient RelationsPatient and Family Advisory CouncilPay My BillVisiting a PatientVisiting Soldiers'Your PrivacyPrograms & Services Programs & ServicesCancer CareChronic DiseaseCritical CareDiagnostic ImagingEmergency ServicesIntegrated Medicine RehabInfection Prevention & ControlLaboratoryMental Health Mental HealthThe Meeting PlacePaediatric Eating Disorder ProgramOutpatient ClinicKidney Care Kidney CareResourcesAsthma CentreWomen & Children Women & ChildrenPaediatricsSexual Assault & Domestic ViolenceGeneticsRehabSurgical ServicesTelemedicineReferrals and RequisitionsJoin Our TeamKnowledge & ResourcesContactNews & EventsStaffStudentsPay My BillBoard Login
Close Menu
PrivacyOrillia Soldiers’ Memorial Hospital (OSMH) (being “we”, “our”, “Hospital” or “OSMH”) is committed to ensuring that the information included on the OSMH website does not contain any personal/personal health information of any individual without their express permission.
Policy:
OSMH places a high value on privacy. To learn more about OSMH’s commitment to protecting the personal information of our patients, please visit the Patient Privacy area of this site. For information on the Terms and Conditions for the use of information on our website, please see Terms and Conditions.
Protection of User’s Personal Information
No personal information is collected from users of this site without prior permission. OSMH does not sell, rent or lease personal information about its customers to third parties.
Server logs
We strive to improve the access, design and functionality of our Site so that you are able to find the information you are seeking easily and quickly. In order to do this, we need to determine what type of information is accessed more frequently, and we may do this by tracking statistics such as IP address, browser type, domain name, access times and referring website addresses. These statistics are used to improve our Site and ensure that it provides an optimal experience for visitors.
Personal Information sent via e-mail
Should you choose to provide personal information through e-mail or other means, the information will only be used for the specific purposes for which it has been provided (e.g. to respond to a specific request, share your story, complete a survey or for employment).
External Web Links
OSMH makes no guarantees as to the Privacy Policy of websites that we link to. You are encouraged to review the privacy statements of the websites you choose to link to from the OSMH Website so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information.
Privacy and Social Media
OSMH is committed to protecting the privacy of our donors, staff and patients. At no time will the Hospital post personal health, employment or financial information, contact information or any other information about family members. Only when consent has been obtained from individual or family, does the Hospital publishes select stories and profiles which include personal information about some of our donors, staff and patients.
You are responsible for protecting your privacy and the privacy of others when using and participating in our social media presence. Be respectful of the privacy of patients, families and staff by not using names when posting comments, or provide any identifying details. Posts that identify OSMH donors, staff, physicians or patients, may be removed.
Questions
If you have questions regarding the Privacy Policy for the OSMH website, or to raise a concern you have with our practices, contact 705-325-2201 ext. 3626.
Search the Site
Search
Close Modal
